In this video, I wanted to give you a few tips and tricks
在本视频中 我将介绍我在制作课程资料时
that I've used while developing some of this material.
采用的一些技巧和方法
SageMaker is a wonderful tool that can really help
SageMaker 是一个很棒的工具
reduce the development time of a lot of machine learning projects.
能够大大缩短很多机器学习项目的开发时间
However, problems can be sometimes difficult to diagnose.
但是 有时候问题难以诊断
We spoke in a previous video about using the CloudWatch Logs,
我们在之前的视频中提到了 CloudWatch 日志
and it's something that I have found very helpful.
我发现 CloudWatch 日志很有用
In particular, say I'm training something,
假设我正在训练某个模型
I can look at the training job,
可以检查训练作业
and see if it has failed.
看看是否失败了
The most recent training jobs here have no failures,
最近的训练作业没有失败
but I can take a look at one of them,
打开一个作业看看
and if I scroll down,
向下滚动
there is a link to the CloudWatch logs, which I can open up.
就能找到 CloudWatch 日志链接 打开它
To take a look at the output that was generated by that training job,
看看该训练作业生成的输出结果
I found this to be very, very helpful.
我发现这些信息很有用
This is especially true when you
如果你在训练模型时
are training a model that allows you to incorporate your own code.
添加了你自己的代码 则尤其有用
For example, any PyTorch model,
例如对于任何 PyTorch 模型
where you get to include your own training method.
你将添加你自己的训练方法
Sometimes errors can occur that are very difficult to diagnose.
有时候会出现问题 并且非常难以诊断
But, taking a look at the output here can be very helpful,
但是查看这些输出结果很有用
especially if you include some additional output in your provided code.
尤其是如果在提供的代码中添加了其他输出的话
Another general trick that I should mention is
另一个常用技巧是
that you should not be afraid of copying and pasting.
可以复制粘贴内容
It is certainly the case that many of the things you need to do inside of
在 SageMaker 中需要完成的很多任务
SageMaker are very similar to other things that you've done outside of SageMaker.
肯定与在 SageMaker 中已经完成的其他任务非常相似
Training a model, for example,
例如 训练模型
sometimes requires a few lines of code,
有时候需要几行代码
but the changes between two different models being trained is typically very small.
但是两个被训练的不同模型之间的差别通常很小
So, copy and paste is your friend.
所以复制粘贴很管用
Another thing I'd like to mention is the documentation.
还有一点要提的是参考文档
The main documentation is this document here,
主要参考文档是这个文档
however, SageMaker, the platform itself, moves very quickly.
但是 SageMaker 平台本身变化非常快
Sometimes more quickly than the documentation.
有时候文档来不及更新
So, you're not always able to find all of
你并非始终能够
the features that are available in the documentation.
在文档里找到所有的功能
It's a fantastic place to look to start,
文档是个不错的参考工具
but sometimes you have to look a little deeper.
但有时候需要更深入地探索
Another useful piece of documentation is the Python SDK.
另一个很实用的文档是 Python SDK
We've been calling this the high-level approach.
它属于高阶方法
In this document sort of a different approach to using SageMaker,
这个文档介绍了使用 SageMaker 的不同方法
which can be helpful as well,
很有用
and this document is also fantastic,
并且这个文档很实用
but at times suffers from the same problem as the previous document in that,
但有时候跟 SageMaker 文档一样
the code-based moves faster than the documentation.
代码变化太快 文档来不及更新
When in doubt, I would say,
如果有疑问的话
don't be afraid to look at the actual codebase itself.
可以看看实际代码库本身
Fortunately it's provided here on GitHub.
代码库位于 GitHub 上
One of the reasons this is really helpful is that
查看代码库很有用的原因之一是
the Python SDK or the high-level approach as I said in a previous video,
Python SDK 或高阶方法
make some choices on your behalf,
会代表你做出一些选择
which can be fantastic because it can reduce the development time,
这很棒 因为可以缩短开发时间
but it can also be a little difficult to
但是也难以诊断问题
diagnose because you're not always sure what's happening.
因为你并非始终知道所发生的情况
If you want to know exactly what's happening,
如果你想确切地了解所发生的情况
checking the actual code can be really helpful.
可以查看实际代码
For example, I can open up the estimator Python file,
例如打开 estimator Python 文件
which will include the description of the estimator class.
其中包含 estimator 类的说明
That way I can scroll down,
向下滚动
and take a look at say,
并看看
what's happening when I try and set some hyper parameters,
当我设置某些超参数或者训练或拟合模型时
or train, or fit the model.
会发生什么
I've actually found looking through the code to be really helpful.
我发现浏览代码很有用
It's also very well documented.
这些代码结构清晰
So, when I get stuck,
当我遇到问题时
that's usually where I turned.
通常都会去看看代码库
One last tip that I'll give you is that most
最后还有一条小技巧
of the problems that I encountered while developing this material,
我在制作这些学习资料时遇到的大部分问题
had to do with naming the various objects that were created.
都与命名创建的各种对象有关
The fact that you need to have a unique name is a blessing and a curse.
唯一名称有好有坏
It is a blessing in that,
好处是
you can reuse many of the objects that you've created at a later time,
之后可以重复使用创建的对象
since each one has a unique name.
因为每个对象都有唯一名称
It can be a curse when you don't
坏处是
quite pay attention to the naming convention that you've been using,
如果不注意命名规则的话
or you're not careful about making sure your names are unique.
或者名称不唯一的话 就会遇到问题
Tips and tricks aside, I hope you enjoy playing with SageMaker. Good luck.
小技巧就讲完了 希望你能喜欢使用 SageMaker加油！